<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/ns/ttml" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/ns/ttml#styling">
  <body>
    <div xml:lang="en">
      <p begin="00:00:00.0" end="00:00:04.0">Wow, the ThankYou® Points in your account are really adding up. </p>
      <p begin="00:00:05.0" end="00:00:09.0">Now you’re ready to redeem them, and you found the perfect item on one of your favorite websites.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:10.0" end="00:00:13.0">But how can ThankYou® Rewards make it easier to get that item?</p>
      <p begin="00:00:14.0" end="00:00:23.0">Citi has an awesome feature that allows you to redeem your points for a statement credit to your credit card account when making a purchase on any site that accepts MasterCard® or Visa®.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:24.0" end="00:00:26.0">It’s called Rewards Account Numbers.</p>
      <p begin="00:00:27.0" end="00:00:33.0">Rewards Account Numbers are temporary virtual credit card numbers linked to your credit card and ThankYou Member Account. </p>
      <p begin="00:00:34.0" end="00:00:36.0">Getting Rewards Account Numbers is easy. Have a look. </p>
      <p begin="00:00:37.0" end="00:00:44.0">Once you log in, click Launch on the Rewards Account Numbers page to begin. In a few simple clicks, you’ll be on your way to purchasing. </p>
      <p begin="00:00:45.0" end="00:00:56.0">On the Generate your Rewards Account Number page, enter the amount of ThankYou Points you’d like to redeem and it will automatically display the statement credit value. Once you’ve entered the amount of points to use click Continue. </p>
      <p begin="00:00:57.0" end="00:00:59.0">Now you’re ready to create your Rewards Account Number.</p>
      <p begin="00:01:00.0" end="00:01:05.0">Rewards Account Numbers can be used to redeem your ThankYou Points for a statement credit up to the total cost of your online purchase. </p>
      <p begin="00:01:06.0" end="00:01:20.0">When using a Rewards Account Number, the transactions will post to your credit card first. And then you’ll receive a statement credit for the amount you requested to redeem. If the ThankYou Points redeemed do not cover the entire amount the balance of the purchase price will remain on your credit card account. </p>
      <p begin="00:01:21.0" end="00:01:32.0">The Rewards Account Number is valid to use as often as you’d like through midnight Pacific time of that day. Next, click Generate and, Presto, your Rewards Account Number is ready to use. </p>
      <p begin="00:01:33.0" end="00:01:44.0">Using Rewards Account Numbers is even easier. Simply copy and paste the new number into the checkout form and enter the three-digit security code and expiration date just like using your regular Citi credit card.</p>
      <p begin="00:01:45.0" end="00:01:56.0">After you place your order there’s nothing more to do. You can visit your account online to view purchases and recent transactions on your credit card account. Your statement credit will appear within 48 hours after your purchase posts.  </p>
      <p begin="00:01:57.0" end="00:02:08.0">If you don’t have enough points to cover the entire cost of the item, the balance of the cost will remain on your credit card. Likewise, any points not applied to the statement credit will remain in your ThankYou member account. </p>
      <p begin="00:02:09.0" end="00:02:15.0">You can also visit thankyou.com and on the order history page you can see all the Rewards Account Numbers activity in one place. </p>
      <p begin="00:02:16.0" end="00:02:19.0">So be sure to use a Rewards Account Number the next time you want to get that perfect item.</p>
      <p begin="00:02:20.0" end="00:02:30.0">Rewards Account Numbers from Citi. For more flexibility in using your ThankYou Points Your Way anywhere MasterCard® and Visa® are accepted.  </p>
    </div>
  </body>
</tt>